Guide to the Transport Workers Union, Local 100: Sarah Goldstein Interviews Oral History Collection OH.047
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Transport Workers Union of America, Local 100: Sarah Goldstein Interviews Oral History Collection
2002-2004
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Goldstein, Sarah
OH.047
1 Linear Feet 29 compact cassette tapes
The Transport Workers Union of America, Local 100: Sarah Goldstein Interviews Oral History Collection (OH 047) contains 17 audio interviews and accompanying printed transcripts. Sarah Goldstein interviews TWU Local 100 members between October 2002 and January 2004, discussing TWU leaadership and the New Directions subgroup.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Sarah Goldstein in 2014. The accession number associated with this collection is 1985.003.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives, special.collections@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596 with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Scope and Contents
The Transport Workers Union (TWU) was founded in 1934 and represents transportation workers in both the public and private sectors. TWU's New York City-based Local 100 represents 41,000 workers, primarily in the New York City public transportation system.
This collection consists of 17 interviews on audiocassette conducted by Sarah Goldstein, and accompanying printed transcripts. Interviewees include TWU Local 100 members involved with the progressive New Directions faction, including Marc Kagan, as well as then-president of the local Roger Toussaint. Interviews were conducted between October 2002 and January 2004, and subject matter includes differing views on current leadership and the New Directions subgroup.
Goldstein, Sarah
- Acevedo, Noel, August 6, 2003
  - Original Recording (Box Shared Tamiment 101, Audiocassette 1A)
  - Original Recording (Box Shared Tamiment 101, Audiocassette 1B)
  - Transcript (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Kagan, Marc, August 22, 2003
  - Original Recording (Box Shared Tamiment 101, Audiocassette 2A)
  - Original Recording (Box Shared Tamiment 101, Audiocassette 2B)
  - Transcript (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Kagan, Marc, January 28, 2004
  - Original Recording (Box Shared Tamiment 101, Audiocassette 3A)
  - Original Recording (Box Shared Tamiment 101, Audiocassette 3B)
  - Transcript (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Allen, Naomi, August 4, 2003
  - Original Recording (Box Shared Tamiment 101, Audiocassette 4A)
  - Original Recording (Box Shared Tamiment 101, Audiocassette 4B)
  - Transcript (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Cassano, Thomas, July 1, 2003
  - Original Recording (Box Shared Tamiment 101, Audiocassette 5A)
  - Original Recording (Box Shared Tamiment 101, Audiocassette 5B)
  - Transcript (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Diaz, Eladio, October 18, 2002
  - Original Recording (Box Shared Tamiment 101, Audiocassette 6)
  - Transcript (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Downs, Steve, November 27, 2002
  - Original Recording (Box Shared Tamiment 101, Audiocassette 7A)
  - Original Recording (Box Shared Tamiment 101, Audiocassette 7B)
  - Transcript (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Downs, Steve, January 2003
  - Original Recording (Box Shared Tamiment 101, Audiocassette 8)
  - Transcript (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Fraidstern, Josh, July 15, 2003
  - Original Recording (Box Shared Tamiment 101, Audiocassette 9A)
  - Original Recording (Box Shared Tamiment 101, Audiocassette 9B)
  - Transcript (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Fraidstern, Josh, January 14, 2004
  - Original Recording (Box Shared Tamiment 101, Audiocassette 10)
  - Transcript (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Little, Clarence, July 30, 2003
  - Original Recording (Box Shared Tamiment 101, Audiocassette 11A)
  - Original Recording (Box Shared Tamiment 101, Audiocassette 11B)
  - Transcript (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Lawson, Darlyne, June 24, 2003
  - Original Recording (Box Shared Tamiment 101, Audiocassette 12)
  - Transcript (Box 1, Folder 11)
- McMillon, Julia, June 22, 2003
  - Original Recording (Box Shared Tamiment 101, Audiocassette 13A)
  - Original Recording (Box Shared Tamiment 101, Audiocassette 13B)
  - Transcript (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Schulman, Roy, June 25, 2003
  - Original Recording (Box Shared Tamiment 101, Audiocassette 14A)
  - Original Recording (Box Shared Tamiment 101, Audiocassette 14B)
  - Transcript (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Swerdlow, Marian, July 16, 2003
  - Original Recording (Box Shared Tamiment 101, Audiocassette 15A)
  - Original Recording (Box Shared Tamiment 101, Audiocassette 15B)
  - Transcript (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Toussaint, Roger, August 7, 2003
  - Original Recording (Box Shared Tamiment 101, Audiocassette 16A)
  - Original Recording (Box Shared Tamiment 101, Audiocassette 16B)
  - Transcript (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Wilson, Liz, June 17, 2003
  - Original Recording (Box Shared Tamiment 101, Audiocassette 17)
  - Transcript (Box 1, Folder 16)